Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
1750-1990
Harvard College Observatory.
KG11365-6
118 cubic feet 118 boxes
2518 volumes
- Transit Circle, 1848-11-07 to 1849-07-30; KG11365.1 (Box 1)
  Additional identifier
  Also identified as: A1.
  Annotated May 1854.
- Transit Circle, 1849-07-30 to 1849-09-25; KG11365.2 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A2.
- Transit Circle, 1849-09-26 to 1849-11-29; KG11365.3 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A3.
  Author/s
  William Cranch Bond.
- Transit Circle, 1849-11-30 to 1850-02-06; KG11365.4 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A4.
  Benjamin Peirce.
  Pierce's involvement uncertain.
- Transit Circle, 1850-02-06 to 1850-04-30; KG11365.5 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A5.
  Charles W. Tuttle.
- Transit Circle, 1850-05-01 to 1850-10-20; KG11365.6 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A6.
- Transit Circle, 1850-10-21 to 1850-12-26; KG11365.7 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A7.
- Transit Circle [Electric Telegraph], 1850-12-26 to 1851-04-03; KG11365.8 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A8.
- Transit Circle, 1851-04-03 to 1851-07-13; KG11365.9 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A9.
- Transit Circle [Solar Eclipse 7/28], 1851-07-13 to 1851-09-05; KG11365.10 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A10.
  Photographs (daguerreotype).
- Transit Circle [Asteroids], 1851-09-05 to 1852-01-15; KG11365.11 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A11.
- Transit Circle, 1852-01-15 to 1852-06-28; KG11365.12 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A12.
- Transit Circle, 1852-06-28 to 1852-12-05; KG11365.13 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A13.
- Transit Circle, 1852-12-01 to 1853-07-08; KG11365.14 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A14.
- Transit Circle, 1853-07-08 to 1854-02-26; KG11365.15 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A15.
- Transit Circle, 1854-02-28 to 1854-08-15; KG11365.16 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A16.
- Transit Circle, 1854-08-15 to 1854-11-27; KG11365.17 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A17.
- Transit Circle, 1854-11-27 to 1855-01-25; KG11365.18 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A18.
- Transit Circle, 1855-01-25 to 1855-05-06; KG11365.19 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A19.
- Transit Circle, 1855-05-06 to 1855-07-31; KG11365.20 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A20.
- Transit Circle, 1855-08-01 to 1855-09-25; KG11365.21 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A21.
- Transit Circle [Eclipse], 1855-09-25 to 1856-03-27; KG11365.22 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A22.
- Transit Circle, 1856-03-27 to 1856-06-15; KG11365.23 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A23.
- Transit Circle, 1856-06-16 to 1856-09-05; KG11365.24 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A24.
- Transit Circle, 1856-09-08 to 1857-02-09; KG11365.25 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A25.
- Transit Circle, 1857-02-17 to 1857-09-21; KG11365.26 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A26.
- Transit Circle, 1857-09-21 to 1857-11-03; KG11365.27 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A27.
- Transit Circle, 1857-11-03 to 1858-02-10; KG11365.28 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A28.
- Transit Circle, 1858-02-10 to 1858-07-05; KG11365.29 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A29.
- Transit Circle, 1858-07-05 to 1859-01-24; KG11365.30 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A30.
- Transit Circle, 1859-01-24 to 1859-08-17; KG11365.31 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A31.
- Transit Circle, 1859-08-17 to 1860-01-23; KG11365.32 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A32.
- Transit Circle, 1860-01-23 to 1860-06-23; KG11365.33 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A33.
- Transit Circle, 1860-06-23 to 1860-11-29; KG11365.34 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A34.
- Transit Circle, 1860-11-29 to 1861-03-21; KG11365.35 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A35.
- Transit Circle, 1861-03-21 to 1861-10-01; KG11365.36 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A36.
- Transit Circle, 1861-10-01 to 1862-03-28; KG11365.37 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A37.
- Meridian Circle, 1862-03-28 to 1862-05-07; KG11365.38 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A38.
- Meridian Circle, 1862-05-07 to 1862-08-06; KG11365.39 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A39.
- Meridian Circle, 1862-08-11 to 1862-09-25; KG11365.40 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A40.
- Meridian Circle, 1862-09-27 to 1862-12-08; KG11365.41 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A41.
- Meridian Circle, 1862-12-10 to 1863-02-16; KG11365.42 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A42.
- Meridian Circle, 1863-02-17 to 1863-05-25; KG11365.43 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A43.
- Meridian Circle, 1863-05-26 to 1863-08-14; KG11365.44 (Box 1)
  Also identified as: A44.
- Meridian Circle, 1863-08-14 to 1863-09-22; KG11365.45 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A45.
- Meridian Circle, 1863-09-23 to 1863-12-02; KG11365.46 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A46.
- Meridian Circle, 1863-12-05 to 1864-01-11; KG11365.47 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A47.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-01-11 to 1864-03-03; KG11365.48 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A48.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-03-07 to 1864-04-09; KG11365.49 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A49.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-04-09 to 1864-05-19; KG11365.50 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A50.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-05-22 to 1864-06-06; KG11365.51 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A51.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-06-07 to 1864-06-19; KG11365.52 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A52.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-06-21 to 1864-07-05; KG11365.53 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A53.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-07-06 to 1864-07-19; KG11365.54 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A54.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-07-20 to 1864-09-09; KG11365.55 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A55.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-09-10 to 1864-10-10; KG11365.56 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A56.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-10-10 to 1864-11-04; KG11365.57 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A57.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-11-10 to 1864-11-23; KG11365.58 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A58.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-11-25 to 1864-12-20; KG11365.59 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A59.
- Meridian Circle, 1864-12-30 to 1865-01-18; KG11365.60 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A60.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-01-20 to 1865-02-01; KG11365.61 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A61.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-02-02 to 1865-02-25; KG11365.62 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A62.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-02-27 to 1865-04-03; KG11365.63 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A63.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-04-03 to 1865-04-26; KG11365.64 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A64.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-05-01 to 1865-06-02; KG11365.65 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A65.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-06-03 to 1865-07-04; KG11365.66 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A66.
- Meridian Circle, 1868-07-05 to 1865-07-18; KG11365.67 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A67.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-07-20 to 1865-08-01; KG11365.68 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A68.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-08-02 to 1865-08-28; KG11365.69 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A69.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-08-29 to 1865-09-15; KG11365.70 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A70.
- Meridian Circle, 1865-09-16 to 1865-09-30; KG11365.71 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: A71.
- Reduction of Transits, 1849-01-01 to 1849-08-16; KG11365.72 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B1.
- Reduction of Transits, 1849-08-16 to 1849-12-07; KG11365.73 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B2.
- Reduction of Transits, 1849-12-07 to 1850-04-02; KG11365.74 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B3.
- Reduction of Transits, 1850-04-02 to 1850-10-05; KG11365.75 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B4.
- Reduction of Transits, 1850-10-05 to 1850-12-30; KG11365.76 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B5.
- Reduction of Transits, 1850-12-30 to 1851-04-05; KG11365.77 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B6.
- Reduction of Transits, 1851-04-05 to 1851-07-08; KG11365.78 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B7.
- Reduction of Transits, 1851-07-08 to 1851-09-04; KG11365.79 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B8.
- Reduction of Transits, 1851-09-04 to 1851-11-11; KG11365.80 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B9.
- Reduction of Transits, 1851-11-11 to 1852-02-25; KG11365.81 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B10.
- Reduction of Transits, 1852-02-25 to 1852-07-06; KG11365.82 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B11.
- Reduction of Transits, 1852-07-06 to 1852-11-17; KG11365.83 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B12.
- Reduction of Transits, 1852-11-17 to 1853-05-01; KG11365.84 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B13.
- Reduction of Transits, 1853-05-01 to 1853-11-02; KG11365.85 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B14.
- Reduction of Transits, 1853-11-02 to 1854-04-04; KG11365.86 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B15.
- Reduction of Transits, 1854-04-04 to 1854-08-09; KG11365.87 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B16.
- Reduction of Transits, 1854-08-06 to 1854-11-27; KG11365.88 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B17.
- Reduction of Transits, 1854-11-27 to 1855-01-30; KG11365.89 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B18.
- Reduction of Transits, 1855-01-30 to 1855-05-06; KG11365.90 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B19.
- Reduction of Transits, 1855-05-06 to 1855-08-01; KG11365.91 (Box 2)
  Also identified as: B20.
- Reduction of Transits, 1855-07-31 to 1855-09-25; KG11365.92 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B21.
- Reduction of Transits, 1855-09-25 to 1856-03-30; KG11365.93 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B22.
- Reduction of Transits, 1856-03-30 to 1856-06-11; KG11365.94 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B23.
- Reduction of Transits, 1856-06-11 to 1856-08-22; KG11365.95 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B24.
- Reduction of Transits, 1856-08-22 to 1856-11-20; KG11365.96 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B25.
- Reduction of Transits, 1856-11-20 to 1857-04-30; KG11365.97 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B26.
- Reduction of Transits, 1857-04-30 to 1857-10-04; KG11365.98 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B27.
- Reduction of Transits, 1857-10-04 to 1857-11-28; KG11365.99 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B28.
- Reduction of Transits, 1857-11-28 to 1858-02-23; KG11365.100 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B29.
- Reduction of Transits, 1858-02-23 to 1858-06-24; KG11365.101 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B30.
- Reduction of Transits, 1858-06-24 to 1858-11-09; KG11365.102 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B31.
- Reduction of Transits, 1858-11-09 to 1859-06-19; KG11365.103 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B32.
- Reduction of Transits, 1859-06-19 to 1859-10-14; KG11365.104 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B33.
- Reduction of Transits, 1859-10-14 to 1860-03-27; KG11365.105 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B34.
- Reduction of Transits, 1860-03-27 to 1860-11-16; KG11365.106 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B35.
- Reduction of Transits, 1860-11-16 to 1861-01-01; KG11365.107 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: B36.
- North and South Meridian Marks and Level Readings, 1849-12-05 to 1853-07-04; KG11365.108 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C1.
- North and South Meridian Marks and Level Readings, 1853-07-01 to 1855-04-21; KG11365.109 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C2.
- North and South Meridian Marks and Level Readings, 1855-04-21 to 1856-09-08; KG11365.110 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C3.
- North and South Meridian Marks and Level Readings, 1856-09-01 to 1859-02-24; KG11365.111 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C4.
- North and South Meridian Marks and Level Readings, 1859-02-24 to 1862-03-11; KG11365.112 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C5.
- Instrumental Corrections, 1863-12-29 to 1865-10-01; KG11365.113 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C8.
- Computed AR of Polar Stars, 1862-03-11 to 1863-08-19; KG11365.114 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C9.
- Computed AR of Polar Stars, 1863-08-22 to 1864-11-14; KG11365.115 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C10.
- Chronograph Record, 1861-06-01 to 1863-07-01; KG11365.116 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C11.
- Chronograph Record, 1863-07-23 to 1864-11-04; KG11365.117 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C12.
- Chronograph Record, 1864-11-10 to 1865-09-12; KG11365.118 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C13.
- Chronograph Record, 1865-09-13 to 1866-02-20; KG11365.119 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C14.
- Miscellaneous time observations, KG11365.120 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: C12[C15].
- Minutes of Chronometer Expect., 1849-04-01 to 1850-02-01; KG11365.121 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: D1.
  Includes correspondence with Professor J. Wenlock (Identity uncertain).
- Meridian Circle, 1859-11-07 to 1860-05-25; KG11365.122 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E1.
- Meridian Circle, 1859-05-24 to 1859-11-03; KG11365.123 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E2.
- Meridian Circle, 1860-05-25 to 1860-11-13; KG11365.124 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E3.
- Declinations, 1862-12-20 to 1863-09-09; KG11365.125 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E4.
- Declinations, 1863-09-14 to 1864-10-17; KG11365.126 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E5.
- New Observations, Transit Circle [Venus], 1857-02-17 to 1858-05-28; KG11365.127 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E6.
- Transit Circle, 1851 to 1853; KG11365.128 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E7.
- Transit Circle, 1851-08-07 to 1851-12-04; KG11365.129 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: E8.
- Moon Culminations and Transits, Comets, 1845-12-01 to 1846-04-01; KG11365.130 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F1.
- Comets and Meridian Transits [Earthquake 8/25/1846], 1846-04-01 to 1846-10-01; KG11365.131 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F2.
- Comets and Meridian Transits, 1846-10-01 to 1847-04-16; KG11365.132 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F3.
- Comets and Meridian Transits, 1847-04-24 to 1848-02-09; KG11365.133 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F4.
- Comets and Meridian Transits, 1848-02-18 to 1848-08-01; KG11365.134 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F5.
- Comets and Meridian Transits, 1849-08-01 to 1850-02-27; KG11365.135 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F6.
- Meridian and Prime Vertical Observations, 1844-11-06 to 1844-12-12; KG11365.136 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F7.
- West Transit, 1851-11-05 to 1851-12-16; KG11365.137 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F8.
- Prime Vertical, 1854-11-18; KG11365.138 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F9.
- Magnetic and Prime Vertical, 1858; KG11365.139 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F10.
- Terrestrial Magnetism, 1858-03-25 to 1861-06-05; KG11365.140 (Box 3)
  Also identified as: F11.
- Chronograph, 1864-06-08 to 1864-07-21; KG11365.141 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: F12a.
- Prime vertical computation of Latitude, 1864; KG11365.142 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: F12b.
- Telegraph, 1848-07-06 to 1848-10-28; KG11365.143 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: F13.
- Chronometers, 1851-10-06 to 1853-07-01; KG11365.144 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G1.
- Chronometers (Annular Eclipse 5/26/1854), 1853-07-01 to 1855-04-21; KG11365.145 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G2.
- Sidereal and Mean Time Clocks, 1856-04-21 to 1856-01-01; KG11365.146 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G3.
- Sidereal and Mean Time Clocks, 1856-01-01 to 1857-02-27; KG11365.147 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G4.
- Sidereal and Mean Time Clocks, 1857-02-27 to 1856-07-02; KG11365.148 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G5.
- Sidereal and Mean Time Clocks, 1856-07-02 to 1860-07-16; KG11365.149 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G6.
- Sidereal and Mean Time Clocks, 1860-07-16 to 1862-09-03; KG11365.150 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G7.
- Sidereal and Mean Time Clocks, 1862-09-16 to 1866-03-02; KG11365.151 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: G8.
- Raliroad Time Commenced, 1854-06-29 to 1854-10-01; KG11365.152 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: Ga.
- Trials of Pendulums and Chronometers, 1857-04-27 to 1859-02-19; KG11365.153 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: Gb.
- [Comets and Double Stars], Volume 1, 1848-11-01 to 1849-02-01; KG11365.154 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: Ha.
- Equatorial Reductions, 1860-06-21 to 1861-01-22; KG11365.155 (Box 4)
- Equatorial, Volume 1, 1846-10-01 to 1847-07-01; KG11365.156 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H1.
- Equatorial, Volume 1, 1847-07-01 to 1847-12-01; KG11365.157 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H2.
- Equatorial, Volume 1, 1847-12-01 to 1848-08-01; KG11365.158 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H3.
- Equatorial, Volume 1, 1847-11-01 to 1848-02-01; KG11365.159 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H4.
- Equatorial, Volume 1, 1848-02-01 to 1848-09-01; KG11365.160 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H5.
- Equatorial, Volume 1, 1848-05-01 to 1848-11-01; KG11365.161 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H6.
- Equatorial, Volume 2, 1849-02-01 to 1849-06-01; KG11365.162 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H7.
- Equatorial, Volume 2, 1849-01-01 to 1849-11-01; KG11365.163 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H8.
- Equatorial, Volume 2 [Daguerreotyping], 1849-12-01 to 1850-04-01; KG11365.164 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H10.
- Equatorial, Volume 2, 1850-05-10 to 1850-09-01; KG11365.165 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H11.
- Equatorial, Volume 2, 1850-09-21 to 1851-02-25; KG11365.166 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H12.
- Equatorial, Volume 2, 1851-02-25 to 1851-12-04; KG11365.167 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H13.
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1851-12-04 to 1852-05-18; KG11365.168 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H14.
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1852-05-19 to 1852-10-26; KG11365.169 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H15.
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1852-10-28 to 1853-03-10; KG11365.170 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H16.
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1853-03-10 to 1854-04-04; KG11365.171 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H17.
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1854-04-04 to 1855-06-13; KG11365.172 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H18.
- Equatorial, Volume 3, 1855-06-13 to 1856-04-01; KG11365.173 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H19.
- Equatorial, 1856-04-01 to 1857-02-15; KG11365.174 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H20.
- Equatorial, 1857-02-15 to 1857-05-13; KG11365.175 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H21.
- Equatorial, 1857-05-13 to 1857-08-23; KG11365.176 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H22.
- Equatorial, 1857-08-23 to 1857-10-20; KG11365.177 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H23.
- Equatorial, 1857-10-20 to 1857-12-15; KG11365.178 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H24.
- Equatorial, 1857-12-15 to 1858-03-18; KG11365.179 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H25.
- Equatorial, 1858-03-18 to 1858-07-14; KG11365.180 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H26.
- Equatorial, 1858-07-14 to 1858-09-25; KG11365.181 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H27.
- Equatorial, 1858-09-25 to 1858-11-11; KG11365.182 (Box 4)
  Also identified as: H28.
- Equatorial, 1858-11-11 to 1859-05-04; KG11365.183 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H29.
- Equatorial, 1859-05-04 to 1859-10-26; KG11365.184 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H30.
- Equatorial, 1859-10-26 to 1860-01-31; KG11365.185 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H31.
- Equatorial, 1860-01-31 to 1860-03-15; KG11365.186 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H32.
- Equatorial, 1860-03-15 to 1860-03-30; KG11365.187 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H33.
- Equatorial, 1860-03-30 to 1860-05-02; KG11365.188 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H34.
- Equatorial, 1860-05-02 to 1860-06-24; KG11365.189 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H35.
- Equatorial, 1860-06-24 to 1860-07-04; KG11365.190 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H36.
- Equatorial, 1860-07-04 to 1860-09-26; KG11365.191 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H37.
- Equatorial, 1860-09-26 to 1861-01-31; KG11365.192 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H38.
- Equatorial, 1861-01-31 to 1861-04-09; KG11365.193 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H39.
- Equatorial, 1861-04-09 to 1861-05-03; KG11365.194 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H40.
- Equatorial, 1861-05-03 to 1861-06-22; KG11365.195 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H41.
- Equatorial, 1861-06-22 to 1861-07-13; KG11365.196 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H42.
- Equatorial, 1861-07-13 to 1861-09-16; KG11365.197 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H43.
- Equatorial, 1861-09-16 to 1862-01-01; KG11365.198 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H44.
- Equatorial, 1862-01-01 to 1862-04-19; KG11365.199 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H45.
- Equatorial, 1862-04-19 to 1862-07-06; KG11365.200 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H46.
- Equatorial, 1862-07-06 to 1862-08-19; KG11365.201 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H47.
- Equatorial, 1862-08-19 to 1862-12-06; KG11365.202 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H48.
- Equatorial, 1862-12-06 to 1863-04-13; KG11365.203 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H49.
- Equatorial, 1863-04-13 to 1863-06-10; KG11365.204 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H50.
- Equatorial, 1863-06-10 to 1863-10-05; KG11365.205 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H51.
- Equatorial, 1863-10-05 to 1864-02-19; KG11365.206 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H52.
- Equatorial, 1864-02-19 to 1864-03-21; KG11365.207 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H53.
- Equatorial, 1864-03-21 to 1864-06-01; KG11365.208 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H54.
- Equatorial, 1864-06-01 to 1865-04-03; KG11365.209 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H55.
- Equatorial, 1865-04-03 to 1866-02-05; KG11365.210 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: H56.
  Equatorial series begins again at KG11365.284 (N1).
- Zones 1-7, 1852-04-07 to 1852-05-04; KG11365.211 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K1.
- Zones 7-13, 1852-05-04 to 1852-11-04; KG11365.212 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K2.
- Zones 14-19, Bessel, 1852-11-04 to 1852-12-15; KG11365.213 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K3.
- Zones 20-26, 1852-12-15 to 1853-01-11; KG11365.214 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K4.
- Zones 27-33, 1853-01-11 to 1853-02-12; KG11365.215 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K5.
- Zones 34-39, 1853-02-12 to 1853-03-16; KG11365.216 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K6.
- Zones 40-45, 1853-03-16 to 1853-04-08; KG11365.217 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K7.
- Zones 46-54, 1853-04-08 to 1854-12-08; KG11365.218 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K8.
- Zones 55-62, 1853-05-31 to 1854-09-27; KG11365.219 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K9.
- Zones 65-84a, 1854-09-27 to 1854-12-08; KG11365.220 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K10.
- Zones 84a-88, 1854-12-08 to 1855-02-12; KG11365.221 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K11.
- Zones 89-100, 1855-02-12 to 1855-04-23; KG11365.222 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K12.
- Zones 101-116, 1855-04-23 to 1855-07-17; KG11365.223 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K13.
- Zones 1-6, 1859-03-30 to 1859-05-03; KG11365.224 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K14.
- Zones 6-7, 1859-05-03 to 1859-05-23; KG11365.225 (Box 5)
  Also identified as: K15.
- Zones 117-124, 1859-05-23 to 1859-08-29; KG11365.226 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K16.
- Zones 125-135, 1859-08-29 to 1859-11-26; KG11365.227 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K17.
- Zones 134-146, 1859-11-26 to 1860-02-21; KG11365.228 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K18.
- Zones 147-149, 1860-02-21 to 1860-11-20; KG11365.229 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K19.
- Zones, 1860-11-20 to 1860-02-26; KG11365.230 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K20.
- Zones, 1860-02-26 to 1861-04-08; KG11365.231 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K21.
- Zones, 1861-04-08 to 1861-07-11; KG11365.232 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K22.
- Zones, 1861-07-11 to 1861-09-24; KG11365.233 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K23.
- Zones, 1861-09-24 to 1862-10-22; KG11365.234 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K24.
- Zones, 1862-10-22 to 1863-02-18; KG11365.235 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K25.
- Zones, 1863-02-18 to 1864-06-23; KG11365.236 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K26.
- Zones, 1864-06-23 to 1864-09-27; KG11365.237 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K27.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; KG11365.238 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L1.
- Zones, 1864-10-05 to 1864-12-01; KG11365.239 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: K28.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; KG11365.240 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L2.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; KG11365.241 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L3.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; KG11365.242 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L4.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; KG11365.243 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L5.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, 1853; KG11365.244 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L6.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, KG11365.245 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L7.
- Reduction of Zone Observations, KG11365.246 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L8.
- Comparisons of Zones, KG11365.247 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L9.
- Reductions of Zones No Reductions, 1859; KG11365.248 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L10.
- Reductions of Zones Comparison of Magnitudes, 1859; KG11365.249 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L11.
- Special Zones and Magnitudes, KG11365.250 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L12.
- Revision of Zones Magnitudes, KG11365.251 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: L13.
- Reduction of Zones I, KG11365.252 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M2.